Yale Center for British Art printed materials
Yale Center for British Art, Institutional Archives
- Exhibitions
  - Howard Hodgkin: Recent Paintings, 1985-01-16-1985-03-17 (Box 1318, Folder 34)
  - George Stubbs (1724-1806), 1985-02-13-1985-04-07 (Box 1318, Folder 35)
  - The Art of Paul Sandby, 1985-04-10-1985-06-23 (Box 1318, Folder 36)
  - Thoreau's Country, 1985-05-07-1985-06-30 (Box 1318, Folder 37)
  - The Creative Printmaker, 1985-07-09-1985-08-01 (Box 1318, Folder 38)
  - Gilded Scenes and Shining Prospects, 1985-10-09-1985-12-15 (Box 1318, Folder 39)
  - The Drawings of Sir Jeffry Wyatville, 1985-11-12-1986-01-05 (Box 1318, Folder 40)
  - Painting in Focus: George Romney's Flaxman Modeling the Bust of William Hayley, 1985-11-12-1986-01-05 (Box 1318, Folder 41)
  - Stephen Buckley — Paintings: 1969-1985, 1985-12-20-1986-02-16 (Box 1318, Folder 42)
  - Thomas Girtin (1775-1802), 1986-01-21-1986-03-30 (Box 1318, Folder 43)
  - Gwen John (1876-1939), 1986-02-26-1986-04-20 (Box 1318, Folder 44)
  - Robert Mason: Paintings, 1986-04-15-1986-06-15 (Box 1318, Folder 45)
  - Fay Godwin: Land, 1986-05-14-1986-07-13 (Box 1318, Folder 46)
  - John Hubbard: Paintings, 1964-86, 1986-09-03-1986-10-26 (Box 1318, Folder 47)
  - Victorian Childhood in Paintings from the FORBES Magazine Collection, 1986-11-12-1987-01-11 (Box 1318, Folder 48)
  - Acquisitions: The First Decade, 1986-11-19-1987-01-25 (Box 1318, Folder 49)
  - Sir David Wilkie 1785-1841, 1987-01-21-1987-03-15 (Box 1318, Folder 50)
  - Drawings by Henry Gaudier-Brzeska, 1987-02-04-1987-03-29 (Box 1318, Folder 51)
  - Francis Hayman, 1987-04-01-1987-05-31 (Box 1318, Folder 52)
  - Masters of the Sea: British Marine Watercolors, 1987-06-10-1987-08-02 (Box 1318, Folder 53)
  - Drawing in England: From Hilliard to Hogarth, 1987-09-19-1987-11-08 (Box 1318, Folder 54)
  - Donald Cooper: Photographs of the Classic British Theatre, 1987-11-21-1988-01-10 (Box 1318, Folder 55)
  - Garth Evans: Sculpture and Drawings 1979-87, 1988-01-27-1988-03-20 (Box 1318, Folder 56)
  - Hard Times: Victorian Social Realism, 1988-04-06-1988-05-29 (Box 1318, Folder 57)
  - Alexander Pope and His World, 1988-04-08-1988-05-29 (Box 1318, Folder 58)
  - Richard Redgrave, 1988-06-15-1988-08-07 (Box 1318, Folder 59)
  - David Bomberg (1890-1957), 1988-09-10-1988-10-30 (Box 1318, Folder 60)
  - Bloomsbury Artists at Charleston: Paintings from the Reader's Digest Collection, 1988-09-14-1988-10-09 (Box 1318, Folder 61)
  - Victor Pasmore, 1988-11-16-1989-01-08 (Box 1318, Folder 62)
  - The Mapmaker's Art: 300 Years of British Cartography, 1989-01-17-1989-03-12 (Box 1318, Folder 63)
  - Roger Fenton, Photographer of the 1850s, 1989-01-25-1989-03-26 (Box 1318, Folder 64)
  - Light and Landscape: Recent Drawings by David Blackburn, 1989-03-28-1989-05-28 (Box 1318, Folder 65)
  - Fairest Isle: The Appreciation of British Scenery, 1750-1850, 1989-04-12-1989-06-25 (Box 1318, Folder 66)
  - John Golding: Works From a Decade, 1989-09-16-1989-11-12 (Box 1318, Folder 67)
  - Coracle Press, 1989-11-07-1990-01-14 (Box 1318, Folder 68)
  - Frederick H. Evans: The Desired Haven, 1989-12-02-1990-01-28 (Box 1318, Folder 69)
  - John Copley (1875-1950), 1990-02-06-1990-04-01 (Box 1318, Folder 70)
  - Pleasures and Pastimes, 1990-02-21-1990-04-29 (Box 1318, Folder 71)
  - Powder Celestial: Snuff Boxes, 1700-1880, 1990-04-20-1990-06-20 (Box 1318, Folder 72)
  - 20th-century Acquisitions: Works on Paper, 1990-05-23-1990-07-15 (Box 1318, Folder 73)
  - Robert Mason: Broadgate Paintings and Drawings 1989-90, 1990-09-12-1990-11-11 (Box 1318, Folder 74)
  - T.S. Eliot: Four Quartets Evocations by David Finn, 1990-09-21-1990-11-18 (Box 1318, Folder 75)
  - Painting in Focus: Mercier's Five Senses, 1990-12-04-1991-02-03 (Box 1318, Folder 76)
  - Crown Pictorial: Art and the British Monarchy, 1990-12-05-1991-02-17 (Box 1318, Folder 77)
  - Kentucky Scenes, 1991-02-15-1991-04-14 (Box 1318, Folder 78)
  - Pocket Cathedrals: Pre-Raphaelite Book Illustration, 1991-03-06-1991-05-05 (Box 1318, Folder 79)
  - Boswell's Johnson, 1991-04-20-1991-06-09 (Box 1318, Folder 80)
  - Frank Auerbach: To the Studios and Other Works, 1991-05-22-1991-07-14 (Box 1318, Folder 81)
  - Maggi Hambling: An Eye through a Decade, 1991-09-07-1991-10-27 (Box 1318, Folder 82)
  - Richard Parkes Bonington: 'On the Pleasure of Painting', 1991-11-13-1992-01-19 (Box 1318, Folder 83)
  - Peter Nadin: Recent Work, 1992-02-26-1992-03-29 (Box 1318, Folder 84)
  - Roads to Rails: Revolution in British Transport, 1992-04-15-1992-06-28 (Box 1318, Folder 85)
  - Victorian Landscape Watercolors, 1992-09-09-1992-11-01 (Box 1318, Folder 86)
  - Martin Naylor: Selected Work, 1972-1992, 1992-11-21-1993-01-31 (Box 1318, Folder 87)
  - Endangered Craft/ Evolving Art: British Letterpress Today, 1993-02-02-1993-03-07 (Box 1318, Folder 88)
  - Sir Thomas Lawrence: Portraits of an Age, 1790-1830, 1993-02-27-1993-04-25 (Box 1318, Folder 89)
  - The Archaeology of Architecture: C.R. Cockerell in Southern Europe and the Levant, 1810-1817, 1993-03-23-1993-05-23 (Box 1318, Folder 90)
  - Photographs by Horatio Ross, 1801-1886, 1993-09-14-1993-11-28 (Box 1318, Folder 91)
  - Translations: Turner and Printmaking + Photographs by Horatio Ross, 1801-1886, 1993-09-28 (Box 1318, Folder 92)
  - Translations: Turner and Printmaking, 1993-09-29-1993-12-05 (Box 1318, Folder 93)
  - One Man's Henry Moore, 1993-12-11-1994-02-20 (Box 1318, Folder 94)
  - Toil and Plenty: Images of the Agricultural Landscape in England, 1780-1890, 1994-01-15-1994-03-13 (Box 1318, Folder 95)
  - A Struggle for Fame: Victorian Women Artists and Authors, 1994-03-01-1994-05-08 (Box 1318, Folder 96)
  - Tom Phillips, R. A., 1994-04-06-1994-06-12 (Box 1318, Folder 97)
  - James Smetham (1821-1889), 1994-09-13-1994-11-13 (Box 1318, Folder 98)
  - Wenceslaus Hollar: A Bohemian Artist in England, 1994-11-16-1995-01-22 (Box 1318, Folder 99)
  - Fancy Pieces: Genre Mezzotints by Robert Robinson and his Contemporaries, 1994-11-19-1995-02-05 (Box 1364, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Hepworth: A Retrospective, 1995-02-04-1995-04-09; \ (Box 1364, Folder 2)
  - Constance Stuart Larrabee: Time Exposure, 1995-09-08-1995-11-12 (Box 1364, Folder 3)
  - Romantic Vision: Responses to Change, 1995-11-15-1996-01-14 (Box 1364, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary British Printmaking: The Paragon Press 1986-1995, 1995-12-02-1996-02-04 (Box 1364, Folder 5)
  - The Reformation of the Bible/ The Bible of the Reformation, 1996-02-03-1996-04-02 (Box 1364, Folder 6)
  - The Grosvenor Gallery: A Palace of Art in Victorian England, 1996-03-02-1996-04-28 (Box 1364, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth S. Tower Collection of British Drawings and Watercolors, 1996-04-17-1996-06-16 (Box 1364, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Forge: A Retrospective, 1996-05-15-1996-07-14 (Box 1364, Folder 9)
  - The Word Returned: Artist Books by Ken Campbell, 1996-08-03-1996-11-03 (Box 1364, Folder 10)
  - British Art Treasures from Russian Imperial Collections in the Hermitage, 1996-10-05-1997-01-05 (Box 1364, Folder 11)
  - "Among the Whores and Thieves": William Hogarth and the Beggar's Opera, 1997-02-01-1997-04-06 (Box 1364, Folder 12)
  - The Human Form Divine: William Blake from the Paul Mellon Collection, 1997-04-02-1997-07-06 (Box 1364, Folder 13)
  - The Visionary Company: Blake's Contemporaries and Followers, 1997-04-13-1997-07-06 (Box 1364, Folder 14)
  - Gillian Ayres, 1997-05-01-1997-07-06 (Box 1364, Folder 15)
  - Humanist Landscapes: Humphrey Spender's Photo-Documents, 1932-1942, 1997-09-10-1997-11-09 (Box 1364, Folder 16)
  - John Martin: Visions of the Biblical Flood, 1997-09-17-1997-11-30 (Box 1364, Folder 17)
  - Irish Paintings from the Collection of Brian P. Burns, 1997-09-25-1998-01-04 (Box 1364, Folder 18)
  - Francis Bacon: A Retrospective, 1999-01-23-1999-03-21 (Box 1364, Folder 19)
  - Francis Bacon: A Retrospective + Lucian Freud Etchings from the PaineWebber Art Collection + Henry Moore and the Heroic: A Centenary Tribute, 1999-01-23-1999-03-21 (Box 1364, Folder 20)
  - Graphic! British Prints Now, 1999-04-08-1999-06-06 (Box 1364, Folder 21)
  - George Stubbs in the Collection of Paul Mellon, 1999-04-30-1999-09-05 (Box 1364, Folder 22)
  - "Doomed Youth": The Poetry and the Pity of World War I, 1999-06-22-1999-09-26 (Box 1364, Folder 23)
  - John Walker: A Theater of Recollection, 1999-06-22-1999-09-26 (Box 1364, Folder 24)
  - James Tissot: Victorian Life/Modern Love, 1999-11-22-1999-11-28 (Box 1364, Folder 25)
  - A Treasure House in Farmington: The Lewis Walpole Library, 1999-10-15-2000-01-09 (Box 1364, Folder 26)
  - Patrick Caulfield: A Retrospective, 1999-10-27-2000-01-09 (Box 1364, Folder 27)
  - Ruskin: Past: Present: Future, 2000-01-20-2000-02-27 (Box 1364, Folder 28)
  - The Art of Bloomsbury, 2000-05-20-2000-09-03 (Box 1364, Folder 29)
  - Edward Lear and the Art of Travel, 2000-09-20-2001-01-14 (Box 1364, Folder 30)
  - Edward Lear and the Art of Travel + The School of London and Their Friends: The Collection of Elaine and Melvin Merians, 2000-09-20-2001-01-14 (Box 1364, Folder 31)
  - The School of London and Their Friends: The Collection of Melvin and Elaine Merians, 2000-10-11-2001-01-07 (Box 1364, Folder 32)
  - The Paul Mellon Bequest: Treasures of a Lifetime, 2001-02-17-2001-04-29 (Box 1364, Folder 33)
  - The Line of Beauty: British Drawings and Watercolors of the Eighteenth Century, 2001-05-17-2001-09-02 (Box 1364, Folder 34)
  - Great British Paintings from American Collections: Holbein to Hockney, 2001-09-27-2001-12-30 (Box 1364, Folder 35)
  - Wilde Americk: Discovery and Exploration of the New World, 2001-11-27-2001-12-30 (Box 1364, Folder 36)
  - Painted Ladies: Women at the Court of Charles II, 1660-1685, 2002-01-25-2002-03-17 (Box 1364, Folder 37)
  - Paula Rego: Celestina's House, 2002-04-18-2002-07-28 (Box 1364, Folder 38)
  - Cooking the Books: Ron King and Circle Press, 2002-06-15-2002-11-09 (Box 1364, Folder 39)
  - The Romantic Landscape Print: The Chiaroscuro of Nature, 2002-09-25-2002-12-29 (Box 1364, Folder 40)
  - Romantic Watercolor: The Hickman Bacon Collection, 2002-10-10-2003-01-05 (Box 1364, Folder 41)
  - Romantic Watercolor: The Hickman Bacon Collection + The Romantic Landscape Print: The Chiaroscuro of Nature, 2002-10-30 (Box 1364, Folder 42)
  - Romantics & Revolutionaries: Regency Portraits from the National Portrait Gallery, London + The Romantic Print in the Age of Revolutions, 2003-01-22 (Box 1364, Folder 43)
  - The Romantic Print in the Age of Revolutions, 2003-01-23-2003-03-30 (Box 1364, Folder 44)
  - Romantics and Revolutionaries: Regency Portraits from the National Portrait Gallery, London, 2003-01-23-2003-03-30 (Box 1364, Folder 45)
  - Bill Brandt: A Retrospective, 2003-04-16-2003-07-20 (Box 1364, Folder 46)
  - Behold, the Sea Itself, 2003-06-14-2003-09-07 (Box 1364, Folder 47)
  - Taste and Beauty in Three Dimensions: Paul Mellon and British Sculpture, summer 2003 (Box 1364, Folder 48)
  - Company Culture: British Artists and the East India Company 1770-1830, 2003-10-16-2004-01-11 (Box 1364, Folder 49)
  - Traces of India: Photography, Architecture, and the Politics of Representation, 2003-10-16-2004-01-11 (Box 1364, Folder 50)
  - Richard Hamilton: Prints and Multiples, 1939-2002, 2004-02-12-2004-05-24 (Box 1364, Folder 51)
  - The Marble Bust, 2004-02-24-2004-11-09 (Box 1364, Folder 52)
  - The Art of James Ward, 2004-05-21-2004-08-22 (Box 1364, Folder 53)
  - Ocean Flowers: Impressions from Nature in the Victorian Era, 2004-06-12-2004-08-08 (Box 1364, Folder 54)
  - The Poetry of Truth: A.W. Hunt and the Art of Landscape, 2004-09-18-2004-12-12 (Box 1364, Folder 55)
  - The Beauty of Life: William Morris and the Art of Design, 2004-10-14-2005-01-02 (Box 1319, Folder 1)
  - William Hodges 1744-1797, 2005-01-24-2005-04-24 (Box 1319, Folder 2)
  - Nobleness and Grandeur: Forging Historical Landscape in Britain 1760-1850, 2005-01-27-2005-04-24 (Box 1319, Folder 3)
  - Whistler: The Naval Review + Recent Gifts and Acquisitions, 2005-05-19-2005-08-15 (Box 1319, Folder 4)
  - The Worlds of Francis Wheatley, 2005-08-31-2005-12-31 (Box 1319, Folder 5)
  - Sensation and Sensibility: Viewing Gainsborough's Cottage Door, 2005-10-06-2005-12-31 (Box 1319, Folder 6)
  - London: John Virtue, 2006-02-02-2006-04-23 (Box 1319, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Whatman's Mill: Papermaking and the Art of Watercolor in Eighteenth Century Britain, 2006-02-22-2006-06-04 (Box 1319, Folder 8)
  - Imaginative Geographies 1770-1940, 2006-04-15-2006-07-15 (Box 1319, Folder 9)
  - Britannia and Muscovy: English Silver at the Court of the Tsars, 2006-05-25-2006-11-10 (Box 1319, Folder 10)
  - Searching for Shakespeare, 2006-06-23-2006-11-17 (Box 1319, Folder 11)
  - Art and Music in Britain: Four Encounters 1730-1900, 2006-10-05-2006-12-31 (Box 1319, Folder 12)
  - Canaletto in England: A Venetian Artist Abroad 1746-1755, 2006-10-19-2006-12-31 (Box 1319, Folder 13)
  - Howard Hodgkin: Paintings 1992-2007, 2007-01-16-2007-03-17 (Box 1319, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Wright and the Spectacle of Science, 2007-03-30-2007-06-11 (Box 1319, Folder 15)
  - Paul Mellon's Legacy: A Passion for British Art, 2007-04-18-2007-07-29 (Box 1319, Folder 16)
  - Jem Southam: Upton Pyne, 2007-08-28-2007-12-30 (Box 1319, Folder 17)
  - Works by Ori Gersht, 2007-11-06-2007-12-30 (Box 1319, Folder 18)
  - Art and Emancipation in Jamaica: Issac Mendes Belisario and His Worlds, 2007-11-27-2007-12-30 (Box 1319, Folder 19)
  - The Lure of the East: British Orientalist Painting 1830-1925 + Pearls to Pyramids: British Visual Culture and the Levant 1600-1830, 2008-02-06-2008-02-07 (Box 1320, Folder 1)
  - The Lure of the East: British Orientalist Painting, 1830-1925, 2008-02-07-2008-04-27 (Box 1320, Folder 2)
  - Pearls to Pyramids: British Visual Culture and the Levant, 1600-1830, 2008-02-07-2008-04-27 (Box 1320, Folder 3)
  - A New World: England's First View of America, 2008-03-06-2008-06-01 (Box 1320, Folder 4)
  - Art in Focus: Figuring Women: The Female in Modern British Art, 2008-03-28-2008-06-08 (Box 1320, Folder 5)
  - Joseph Wright of Derby in Liverpool, 2008-05-22-2008-08-31 (Box 1320, Folder 6)
  - Great British Watercolors from the Paul Mellon Collection at the Yale Center for British Art, 2008-06-10-2008-09-17 (Box 1320, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin West and the Venetian Secret, 2008-09-18-2009-01-04 (Box 1320, Folder 8)
  - Sun, Wind, and Rain: The Art of David Cox, 2008-10-16-2009-01-04 (Box 1320, Folder 9)
  - Endless Forms: Charles Darwin, Natural Science, and the Visual Arts, 2009-02-12-2009-05-03 (Box 1320, Folder 10)
  - Paintings from the Reign of Victoria: The Royal Holloway Collection, London, 2009-05-07-2009-07-26 (Box 1320, Folder 11)
  - Seascapes: Marine Paintings and Watercolors from the U Collection, 2009-05-28-2009-08-23 (Box 1320, Folder 12)
  - Dalou in England: Portraits of Womanhood 1871-1879, 2009-06-11-2009-08-23 (Box 1320, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Delany and Her Circle, 2009-09-24-2010-01-03 (Box 1320, Folder 14)
  - Promiscuous Assemblage, Friendship & The Order of Things, 2009-09-24-2010-07-18 (Box 1320, Folder 15)
  - Horace Walpole's Strawberry Hill, 2009-10-15-2010-01-03 (Box 1320, Folder 16)
  - Varieties of Romantic Experience: Drawings from the Collections of Charles Ryskamp, 2010-02-04-2010-04-25 (Box 1320, Folder 17)
  - Compass and Rule: Architecture as Mathematical Practice in England 1500-1750, 2010-02-18-2010-05-30 (Box 1320, Folder 18)
  - Art in Focus: Installation, Interpretation, Narration, 2010-03-24-2010-06-27 (Box 1320, Folder 19)
  - Art for All: British Posters for Transport, 2010-05-27-2010-08-15 (Box 1320, Folder 20)
  - Seeing Double: Portraits, Copies, and Exhibitions in 1820s London + Structured Elegance: Bookbindings and Jewelry by Romilly Saumarez Smith, 2010-06-23 (Box 1320, Folder 21)
  - Seeing Double: Portraits, Copies, and Exhibitions in 1820s London, 2010-06-24-2010-09-19 (Box 1320, Folder 22)
  - Structured Elegance: Bookbindings and Jewelry by Romilly Saumarez Smith, 2010-06-24-2010-09-19 (Box 1320, Folder 23)
  - The Independent Eye: Contemporary British Art from the Collection of Samuel and Gabrielle Lurie, 2010-09-16-2011-01-02 (Box 1320, Folder 24)
  - Notes from the Archive: James Frazer Stirling, Architect and Teacher + An Architect's Legacy: James Stirling's Students at Yale, 1959-1983, 2010-10-13 (Box 1320, Folder 25)
  - Notes from the Archive: James Frazer Sterling, Architect and Teacher, 2010-10-14-2011-01-02 (Box 1320, Folder 26)
  - "into the light of things": Rebecca Salter, works 1981–2010, 2011-02-03-2011-05-01 (Box 1324, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Lawrence: Regency Power and Brilliance, 2011-02-24-2011-06-05 (Box 1324, Folder 2)
  - Art in Focus: William III, 2011-04-08-2011-07-31 (Box 1324, Folder 3)
  - Connections, 2011-05-20-2011-09-11 (Box 1324, Folder 4)
  - Adapting the Eye: An Archive of the British in India, 1770-1830, 2011-10-11-2011-12-31 (Box 1324, Folder 5)
  - Johan Zoffany RA: Society Observed, 2011-10-27-2012-02-12 (Box 1324, Folder 6)
  - Making History: Antiquaries in Britain, 2012-02-02-2012-05-27 (Box 1324, Folder 7)
  - Art in Focus: Gazes Returned, The Technical Examination of Early English Panel Painting, 2012-04-13-2012-12-09 (Box 1324, Folder 8)
  - The English Prize: The Capture of the "Westmorland," an Episode of the Grand Tour, 2012-10-04-2013-01-13 (Box 1324, Folder 9)
  - Caro: Close Up, 2012-10-18-2012-12-30 (Box 1324, Folder 10)
  - Reflections on Constable's Cloud Studies: Paintings by Mark Leonard, 2012-11-30-2013-03-10 (Box 1324, Folder 11)
  - Edwardian Opulence: British Art at the Dawn of the Twentieth Century, 2013-02-28-2013-06-02 (Box 1324, Folder 12)
  - Art in Focus: St Ives Abstraction, 2013-04-12-2013-09-29 (Box 1324, Folder 13)
  - Sculpture by Nicola Hicks, 2013-11-14-2014-03-09 (Box 1324, Folder 14)
  - Fame and Friendship: Pope, Roubiliac, and the Portrait Bust in Eighteenth-Century Britain, 2014-02-20-2014-05-19 (Box 1324, Folder 15)
  - Richard Wilson and the Transformation of European Landscape Painting, 2014-03-06-2014-06-01 (Box 1324, Folder 16)
  - Art in Focus: Wales, 2014-04-04-2014-08-10 (Box 1324, Folder 17)
  - "Of Green Leaf, Bird, and Flower": Artists' Books and the Natural World, 2014-05-15-2014-08-10 (Box 1324, Folder 18)
  - Bruce Davidson/Paul Caponigro: Two American Photographers in Britain and Ireland, 2014-06-26-2014-09-14 (Box 1324, Folder 19)
  - Sculpture Victorious: Art in an Age of Invention, 1837–1901, 2014-09-11-2014-11-30 (Box 1324, Folder 20)
  - Figures of Empire: Slavery and Portraiture in Eighteenth-Century Atlantic Britain, 2014-10-02-2014-12-14 (Box 1324, Folder 21)
  - Picture Talking: James Northcote and the Fables, 2014-10-02-2014-12-14 (Box 1324, Folder 22)
  - The Critique of Reason: Romantic Art, 1760-1860, 2015-03-06-2015-07-26 (Box 1324, Folder 23)
  - Moving Earth: "Capability" Brown, Humphry Repton, and the Creation of the English Landscape, 2016-03-07-2016-06-03 (Box 1324, Folder 24)
  - Art in Focus: Relics of Old London, 2016-05-11-2016-08-14 (Box 1324, Folder 25)
  - Britain in the World, 2016-05-11-2019-12-31 (Box 1324, Folder 26)
  - Modernism and Memory: Rhoda Pritzker and the Art of Collecting, 2016-05-11-2016-08-21 (Box 1324, Folder 27)
  - "The Poet of Them All": William Shakespeare and Miniature Designer Bindings from the Collection of Neale and Margaret Albert, 2016-06-16-2016-08-21 (Box 1324, Folder 28)
  - Yinka Shonibare MBE (RA), 2016-09-01-2016-12-11 (Box 1324, Folder 29)
  - Spreading Canvas: Eighteenth-Century British Marine Painting, 2016-09-15-2016-12-04 (Box 1324, Folder 30)
  - Enlightened Princesses: Caroline, Augusta, Charlotte, and the Shaping of the Modern World, 2017-02-02-2017-04-30 (Box 1324, Folder 31)
  - Art in Focus: The British Castle—A Symbol in Stone, 2017-04-07-2017-08-06 (Box 1324, Folder 32)
  - A Decade of Gifts and Acquisitions, 2017-06-01-2017-08-13 (Box 1324, Folder 33)
  - "Things of Beauty Growing": British Studio Pottery, 2017-09-14-2017-12-03-12-04 (Box 1324, Folder 34)
  - The Paston Treasure: Microcosm of the Known World, 2018-02-15-2018-05-27 (Box 1324, Folder 35)
  - Salt and Silver: Early Photography, 1840–1860, 2018-06-28-2018-09-09 (Box 1324, Folder 36)
  - George Shaw: A Corner of a Foreign Field, 2018-10-04-2018-12-30 (Box 1324, Folder 37)